Finding Aid for University of Michigan Faculty and Staff Portraits ca. 1860-ca. 1960
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
University of Michigan Faculty and Staff Portraits circa 1860-1960
Michigan Historical Collections.
4 linear feet
Portrait photographs of University of Michigan faculty, administrators and staff.
9263 Bimu 2
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
Brought together from various sources. The largest portion is from the University of Michigan Library (donor 1278 ).
The collection is open for research.
The core of the Faculty and Staff Portrait collection was originally assembled by the University Library. Over the years individual portraits and small groups of photos were added to the collection from various sources and donors.
This collection contains portraits of about 750 University of Michigan faculty members. It is strongest for people who served on the faculty during the nineteenth century and in the 1930s, although a few portraits as late as about 1960 are included.
In addition to faculty, librarians, and research staff, the collection contains portraits of a few nineteenth-century campus characters, including Robert Howard, the bellringer, Jolly the Janitor, "Doc" Gregor Nagele, the Medical School janitor, and Jimmy Ottley, the campus postman.
The photos are arranged alphabetically. Outsize portraits listed in this finding aid are found in the medium-size photograph collection (UAm) under the name of the person.
Faculty portraits are also found in a number of other collections, including:
Rentschler's Studio (Ann Arbor, Mich.)
Shaw, Wilfred Byron.
Swain, George Robert.
University of Michigan class albums.
University of Michigan. Alumni Association.
University of Michigan. News and Information Service. Series D.
The original negatives of some prints in the Faculty Portrait collection may be found in the Rentschler, Swain, and News and Information Service collections. In addition to these collections, faculty portraits can be found in the records of many schools, colleges, and departments, as well as in the papers of individual faculty members.
Subjects - Visual Material:
University of Michigan--Employees--Portraits.; University of Michigan--Faculty--Portraits.
Genre/Form:
Photographs.
- Photographs
  - Abbe-Curtis
    - Abbe, Cleveland, 1838-1916. (Box 1)
    - Abbot, Waldo, 1888- (Box 1)
    - Abbott, Nathan, 1854-1941. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Charles K. (Charles Kendall), 1835-1902. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Edward Larrabee. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Henry Carter, 1851-1921. (Box 1)
    - Adams, Henry Foster, 1882-1973. (Box 1)
    - Aga-Oglu, Mehmet, 1896-1949. (Box 1)
    - Aigler, Ralph William, 1885-1964. (Box 1)
    - Aiton, Arthur S. (Arthur Scott), 1894-1955. (Box 1)
    - Albeladejo, José M. (Box 1)
    - Allen, John Robins, 1869-1920. (Box 1)
    - Allen, Shirley Walter, 1883- (Box 1)
    - Alt, Glenn Leslie. (Box 1)
    - Altshuler, Samuel Simon, 1902- (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Henry Clay, 1872-1939. (Box 1)
    - Angell, Alexis C. (Alexis Caswell), 1857-1932. (Box 1)
    - Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916. (Box 1)
    - Angell, Robert Cooley, 1899- (Box 1)
    - Angell, Sarah Caswell, 1831-1903. (Box 1)
    - Anning, Norman Herbert. (Box 1)
    - Arndt, Hugo Rudolph. (Box 1)
    - Arneill, James Rae, b. 1869. (Box 1)
    - Attwood, Stephen Stanley, 1897-1965. (Box 1)
    - Ayres, William Leake, 1905- (Box 1)
    - Bacher, Byrl F. (Box 1)
    - Bachman, Werner E. (Werner Emmanuel), 1901-1951. (Box 1)
    - Badger, Walter L. (Walter Lucius), 1886-1958. (Box 1)
    - Badgley, Carl Egbert. (Box 1)
    - Baker, E. (Box 1)
    - Barbour, Willard Titus, 1884-1920. (Box 1)
    - Barker, Ernest F. (Ernest Franklin), 1886-1970. (Box 1)
    - Barker, Paul Shirmer, 1895- (Box 1)
    - Barnes, Ernest Harrison. (Box 1)
    - Barnwell, John Blair, 1895- (Box 1)
    - Barrett, Albert M. (Albert Moore), 1871-1936. (Box 1)
      [also UAm]
    - Bartell, Floyd E., 1883-1961. (Box 1)
    - Bartlett, Barbara Haecker. (Box 1)
    - Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1886-1960. (Box 1)
    - Bassett, Leslie, 1923- (Box 1)
    - Baten, William Dowell, 1892- (Box 1)
    - Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949. (Box 1)
    - Bates, John R. (Box 1)
    - Bedard, William D. (Box 1)
    - Beise, Dorothy. (Box 1)
    - Belknap, Ralph L. (Ralph LeRoy), 1894-1960. (Box 1)
    - Belote, George Harold, 1894- (Box 1)
    - Belser, Carl Wilhelm, 1860-1898. (Box 1)
    - Beman, Wooster Woodruff, 1850-1922. (Box 1)
    - Bement, Newton Silas. (Box 1)
    - Bennett, Wells I. (Wells Ira), 1888-1966. (Box 1)
    - Berg, Birger. (Box 1)
    - Besekirsky, Wassily. (Box 1)
    - Bigelow, Melville Madison, 1846-1921. (Box 1)
    - Bigelow, Samuel Lawrence, 1870-1947. (Box 1)
    - Binkley, Harold C. (Box 1)
    - Bittinger, Ross T. (Box 1)
    - Blackburn, Francis Adelbert, 1845-1923. (Box 1)
    - Blackett, Olin Winthrop, 1895- (Box 1)
    - Blake, Warren E. (Warren Everett) (Box 1)
    - Blicke, Frederick Franklin, 1891- (Box 1)
    - Blume, William W., 1893- (Box 1)
    - Blumenthal, Franz L., 1878- (Box 1)
    - Bockstahler, Oscar L. (Box 1)
    - Bogle, Thomas Ashford, 1852-1921. (Box 1)
    - Boise, James Robinson, 1815-1895. (Box 1)
    - Bonner, Campbell, 1876-1954. (Box 1)
    - Boston, Orlan W. (Orlan William), 1891- (Box 1)
    - Bouchard, Harry, 1889-1954. (Box 1)
    - Boucke, Ewald Augustus, d. 1943. (Box 1)
    - Boudemann, Dallas. (Box 1)
    - Bourland, Benjamin Parsons, b. 1870. (Box 1)
    - Brackett, Robert D. (Box 1)
    - Bradbury, Robert W. (Box 1)
    - Braddock, John Richard. (Box 1)
    - Bradshaw, John W. (Box 1)
    - Bragg, E. M. (Edward M.) (Box 1)
    - Brauer, Roland E. (Box 1)
    - Breakey, William Flemming, 1835-1915. (Box 1)
    - Brewster, James Henry, 1856-1920. (Box 1)
    - Brier, John Crowe. (Box 1)
    - Britton, Harold Hudson. (Box 1)
    - Brockway, L. O. (Lawrence Olin), 1907- (Box 1)
    - Bromage, Arthur W. (Arthur Watson), 1904-1979. (Box 1)
    - Brooks, Datus C. (Box 1)
    - Brown, Charles L. (Box 1)
    - Brown, Everett Somerville, 1886-1964. (Box 1)
    - Brown, George Granger, 1896-1957. (Box 1)
    - Brown, Henry Billings, 1836-1913. (Box 1)
    - Brown, Oliver L. (Box 1)
    - Browne, David Henry [UAm only] (Box 1)
    - Brünnow, Franz Friedrich Ernst, 1821-1891. (Box 1)
    - Buettner, William H. (Box 1)
    - Bukovsky, Paul N. (Box 1)
    - Bull, Hempstead S. (Box 1)
    - Bunker, Robert Emmet, b. 1848. (Box 1)
    - Bunting, Russell Welford, 1881-1962. (Box 1)
    - Burklund, Carl Edwin, 1897-1964. (Box 1)
    - Burr, Hillda. (Box 1)
    - Burroughs, Roy J. (Box 1)
    - Bursley, Joseph Aldrich, 1877-1950. (Box 1)
    - Bursley, Philip Everette, c. 1968. (Box 1)
    - Burt, Benjamin Chapman, 1852-1915. (Box 1)
    - Butler, Orma Fitch, 1874-1938. (Box 1)
    - Butts, William Henry. (Box 1)
    - Byrn, Marshall L. (Box 1)
    - Cady, Calvin Brainard. (Box 1)
    - Calderwood, Howard B. (Box 1)
    - Calhoon, Floyd N. (Box 1)
    - Calvery, Herbert Orion, 1897-1945. (Box 1)
    - Camp, Carl Dudley, 1880- (Box 1)
    - Campbell, Edward DeMille, 1863-1925. (Box 1)
    - Campbell, Harry L. (Harry Linn), b. 1888. (Box 1)
    - Campbell, James V. (James Valentine), 1823-1890. (Box 1)
    - Campbell, Laurie E. (Box 1)
    - Campbell, William Aulls, 1859-1931. (Box 1)
    - Campbell, William Wallace, 1862-1938. (Box 1)
    - Canfield, Arthur Graves, 1859-1947. (Box 1)
    - Cannon, Joseph Henderson. (Box 1)
    - Carey, Clifton O. (Clifton O'Neal), 1875-1963. (Box 1)
    - Carr, Lowell Juilliard, 1885- (Box 1)
    - Carrington, Herbert DeWitt. (Box 1)
    - Carrow, Flemming, 1852-1928. (Box 1)
    - Carrothers, George E., 1880-1966. (Box 1)
    - Carver, Harry Clyde. (Box 1)
    - Champlin, John Wayne, 1831-1901. (Box 1)
    - Chapin, Lucius Delison. (Box 1)
    - Cheever, Byron William, 1841-1888. (Box 1)
    - Cheever, Henry Sylvester. (Box 1)
    - Churchill, Ruel Vance, 1899- (Box 1)
    - Cissell, James Harlan, 1889-1949. (Box 1)
    - Clare, Patience D. (Box 1)
    - Clark, John Emory, d. 1921. (Box 1)
    - Cocker, Benjamin Franklin, 1821-1883. (Box 1)
    - Coe, Carl Jenness, b. 1886. (Box 1)
    - Coffey, Hobart R., 1896-1969. (Box 1)
    - Cole, Harry Newton, 1870- (Box 1)
    - Coller, Frederick A., 1887-1964. (Box 1)
    - Colliau, Henry J. (Box 1)
    - Cooley, Mortimer E. (Mortimer Elwyn), 1855-1944. (Box 1)
    - Cooley, Thomas McIntyre, 1824-1898. (Box 1)
    - Copeland, Royal Samuel, 1868-1938. (Box 1)
    - Cork, James Murle, 1894-1957. (Box 1)
    - Coursey, Richard R. (Box 1)
    - Courtis, Stuart A. (Stuart Appleton), 1874-1969. (Box 1)
    - Cowden, Roy William, 1883-1961. (Box 1)
    - Craig, James Alexander, 1855-1932. (Box 1)
    - Craig, Robert, 1882-1962. (Box 1)
    - Crane, Robert Treat, 1880-1962. (Box 1)
    - Crane, Verner Winslow, 1889- (Box 1)
    - Crittenden, Albert Robinson, 1867-1933. (Box 1)
    - Crosby, Alpheus Benning, d. 1877. (Box 1)
    - Crosby, Elizabeth Caroline, 1888-1983. (Box 1)
    - Cross, Arthur Lyon, 1873-1940. (Box 1)
    - Cuncannon, Paul M. (Box 1)
    - Curtis, Allen Jeremiah, d. 1871. (Box 1)
    - Curtis, Francis D. (Francis Day), b. 1888. (Box 1)
    - Curtis, Heber Doust, 1872-1942. (Box 1)
    - Curtis, William Stanton, 1820-1885. (Box 1)
  - Dahlstrom-Isaacs
    - Dahlstrom, Carl E. W. L. (Box 1)
    - Dalke, Paul D. (Box 1)
    - Darling, Cyrenus Garritt, 1856-1933. (Box 1)
    - Davis, Bradley M. (Bradley Moore), b. 1871. (Box 1)
    - Davis, Calvin Olin, 1871-1954. (Box 1)
    - Davis, Charles Albert, 1861-1916. (Box 1)
    - Davis, Joseph Baker, 1845-1920. (Box 1)
    - Davis, Raymond Cazallis, 1836-1919. (Box 1)
    - Dawson, John Philip. (Box 1)
    - Dearborn, Ned. (Box 1)
    - Decker, Arthur James. (Box 1)
    - De Graff, Benjamin A. (Box 1)
    - De Laguna, Theodore de Leo, 1876-1930. (Box 1)
    - Demmon, Isaac Newton, 1842-1920. (Box 1)
    - Denison, Charles Simeon, 1849-1913. (Box 1)
    - Dennison, David M., 1900-1976. (Box 1)
    - Dennison, Walter, 1869-1917. (Box 1)
    - Densmore, Gail E. (Box 1)
    - Denton, Samuel, 1803-1860. (Box 1)
    - DePont, Paul Rousseau Bellou, 1840-1906. (Box 1)
    - Dewey, Willis Alonzo, 1858- (Box 1)
    - Diamond, Thomas, 1881-1962. (Box 1)
    - Dice, Lee Raymond, 1887-1977. (Box 1)
    - Dickerson, J. C. (Box 1)
    - Dickinson, Edwin Dewitt, 1887-1961. (Box 1)
    - Diekhoff, Tobias Johann Casjen, 1867-1935. (Box 1)
    - Dingman, Reed O. (Box 1)
    - Dodge, R. A. (Russell Alger) (Box 1)
    - Donaldson, Bruce McNaughton, 1891-1940. (Box 1)
    - D'Ooge, Benjamin Leonard, 1860-1940. (Box 1)
    - D'Ooge, Martin Luther, 1839-1915. (Box 1)
    - Dorrance, William Henry, d. 1909. (Box 1)
    - Dorsey, John Morris, 1900- (Box 1)
    - Douglas, Silas Hamilton, 1816-1890. (Box 1)
    - Dow, Earle Wilbur, 1868-1946. (Box 1)
    - Dow, William Gould, 1895- (Box 1)
    - Drake, Joseph Horace, 1860-1947. (Box 1)
    - DuBois, Alfred, 1824-1909. (Box 1)
    - Duffendack, Ora Stanley, 1890- (Box 1)
    - Dunham, Fred Sylvester, 1881-1979. (Box 1)
    - Dunlap, Frederick Levy, b. 1870. (Box 1)
    - Dunning, Silas Wright. (Box 1)
    - Dunster, Edward Swift, 1834-1888. (Box 1)
    - Durfee, Edgar Noble, 1882-1958. (Box 1)
    - Dwyer, John W. (John William), b. 1865. (Box 1)
    - Eardley, A. J. (Armand John), 1901- (Box 2)
    - Eaton, John Wallace, 1886-1948. (Box 2)
    - Eckstein, H. C. (Henry Charles), 1890- (Box 2)
    - Edmonson, James Bartlett, 1882-1954. (Box 2)
    - Edmunds, Charles Wallis, 1873-1941. (Box 2)
    - Edwards, B. E. (Box 2)
    - Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933. (Box 2)
    - Egly, William Henry. (Box 2)
    - Ehlers, George Marion, 1891- (Box 2)
    - Ehlers, John Henry. (Box 2)
    - Ehrhard, Jean Edouard, 1905- (Box 2)
    - Eich, Louis Michael. (Box 2)
    - Eliot, Johan W. (Box 2)
    - Ellis, Howard Sylvester, 1898- (Box 2)
    - Emmons, Walter J. (Box 2)
    - Emswiler, John Edward, b. 1880. (Box 2)
    - Eriksen, Edward Leerdrup. (Box 2)
    - Escott, Edward Brind, b. 1868. (Box 2)
    - Evans, Edward Payson, 1831-1917. (Box 2)
    - Everett, Edward Simpson, b. 1883. (Box 2)
    - Fairbanks, Avard Tennyson, 1897- (Box 2)
    - Fairlie, John Archibald, 1872-1947. (Box 2)
    - Farrell, Stephen John, 1865-1933. (Box 2)
    - Fasquelle, Louis, 1808-1862. (Box 2)
    - Feigenbaum, Jacob. (Box 2)
    - Felch, Alpheus, 1804-1896. (Box 2)
    - Feldman, Horace W. (Box 2)
    - Fessenden, Charles Horace, 1885-1934. (Box 2)
    - Field, Irene R. (Box 2)
    - Field, Peter, b. 1876. (Box 2)
    - Field, Shirley Ernest. (Box 2)
    - Finney, Byron Alfred, 1849-1938. (Box 2)
    - Fleischman, Earl E. (Box 2)
    - Florer, Warren Washburn, 1869-1958. (Box 2)
    - Ford, Robert Spivey, 1902- (Box 2)
    - Ford, Walter Burton1874- (Box 2)
    - Forsythe, Warren Ellsworth, 1885-1960. (Box 2)
    - Fralick, F. Bruce. (Box 2)
    - Franklin, Edward Carroll, d. 1885. (Box 2)
    - Franklin, Roswell E. (Box 2)
    - Fraser, Mowat G. (Box 2)
    - Frayer, William Alley. (Box 2)
    - Freer, Paul Caspar, 1862-1912. (Box 2)
    - Freyberg, Woldemar O. (Box 2)
    - Friedgood, Harry B. (Box 2)
    - Fries, Charles Carpenter, 1887- (Box 2)
    - Frieze, Henry S. (Henry Simmons), 1817-1889. (Box 2)
    - Frothingham, George Edward, 1836-1900. (Box 2)
    - Furstenberg, Albert Carl, 1890-1969. (Box 2)
    - Gaige, Frederick M. (Box 2)
    - Gaiss, Aloysius Joseph, 1895- (Box 2)
    - Gatchell, Charles, 1850-1910. (Box 2)
    - Gates, Clare. (Box 2)
    - Gault, Edgar Howard, 1896- (Box 2)
    - Gault, James S. (Box 2)
    - Gayley, Charles Mills, 1858-1932. (Box 2)
    - Gearhart, Roy H. (Box 2)
    - Genthe, Karl Wilhelm. (Box 2)
    - Georg, Conrad. (Box 2)
    - Gibbes, Heneage. (Box 2)
    - Gilmore, Melvin R. (Melvin Randolph), 1868-1940. (Box 2)
    - Glaser, Otto Charles, 1880- (Box 2)
    - Glover, Clifford Conklin. (Box 2)
    - Glover, James Waterman, 1868-1941. (Box 2)
    - Goddard, Edwin Charles, 1865-1942. (Box 2)
    - Gomberg, Moses, 1866-1947. (Box 2)
    - Good, Charles Winfred. (Box 2)
    - Good, Warren Randall, 1900- (Box 2)
    - Goodrich, Carter, 1897-1971. (Box 2)
    - Goodrich, Francis Lee Dewey, 1877-1962. (Box 2)
    - Gordy, Charles Burton. (Box 2)
    - Goulding, Herbert Jay. (Box 2)
    - Graham, Samuel Alexander, 1891- (Box 2)
    - Gram, Lewis M. (Box 2)
    - Green, Frederick May. (Box 2)
    - Greene, Albert Emerson, 1872- (Box 2)
    - Greene, Charles Ezra, 1842-1903. (Box 2)
    - Greene, Katharine B. (Box 2)
    - Greene, William Warren. (Box 2)
    - Greenman, Emerson Frank, 1895-1973. (Box 2)
    - Griffin, Clare Elmer, 1892- (Box 2)
    - Griffin, Levi Thomas, 1837-1906. (Box 2)
    - Griffitts, Charles Hurlburt. (Box 2)
    - Griggs, Earl Leslie, 1899- (Box 2)
    - Grimes, George Lyman. (Box 2)
    - Grismore, Grover Cleveland. (Box 2)
    - Gustafson, Felix G. (Box 2)
    - Guthe, Carl Eugen, 1893- (Box 2)
    - Guthe, Karl Eugen, 1866-1915. (Box 2)
    - Haber, William, 1899- (Box 2)
    - Hadley, Philip Bardwell. (Box 2)
    - Hall, Albert John. (Box 2)
    - Hall, Asaph, 1859-1930. (Box 2)
    - Hall, Louis Phillips, 1860-1941. (Box 2)
    - Hall, Ralph C. (Box 2)
    - Hall, Robert Burnett, 1896-1975. (Box 2)
    - Halstead, William P., 1906- (Box 2)
    - Hamilton, Jean. (Box 2)
    - Hammet, Ralph W. (Box 2)
    - Handman, Max Sylvius, 1885-1939. (Box 2)
    - Harbison, Robert. (Box 2)
    - Harrington, Mark Walrod, 1848-1926. (Box 2)
    - Hartwig, Marie D., 1906- (Box 2)
    - Hassinger, Ruth M. (Box 2)
    - Haven, Erastus Otis, 1820-1881. (Box 2)
    - Hawley, Ransom Smith. (Box 2)
    - Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1887-1945. (Box 2)
    - Hazelton, William Sylvester. (Box 2)
    - Hébrard, Jean, 1878-1959. (Box 2)
    - Heilbrunn, Lewis Victor, 1892- (Box 2)
    - Hellwarth, Arlen R. (Box 2)
    - Hempl, George, 1859-1921. (Box 2)
    - Hench, George Allison, 1866-1899. (Box 2)
    - Henderson, William D., 1866-1944. (Box 2)
    - Heneman, Harlow James. (Box 2)
    - Hennequin, Alfred, 1846-1914. (Box 2)
    - Higbie, Henry Harold, b. 1882. (Box 2)
    - Hildner, Jonathan August Charles. (Box 2)
    - Hilgard, Eugene W. (Eugene Woldemar), 1833-1916. (Box 2)
    - Hill, Theron S. (Box 2)
    - Hinsdale, W. B. (Wilbert B.), 1851-1944. (Box 2)
    - Hoad, William Christian, 1874-1962. (Box 2)
    - Hodges, Fred Jenner, 1895- (Box 2)
    - Hoff, Neville Soule, 1854-1926. (Box 2)
    - Holbrook, Evans, 1875-1932. (Box 2)
    - Holland, Lewis N. (Box 2)
    - Hollands, William Charles, b. 1862. (Box 2)
    - Hollister, Richard Dennis Teall, 1878- (Box 2)
    - Hopkins, Anderson Hoyt, 1861-1917. [UAm only] (Box 2)
    - Hopkins, Louis Allen. (Box 2)
    - Housel, William S. (William Stuart), 1901-1978. (Box 2)
    - Howard, Robert [bellringer] (Box 2)
    - Hubbs, Carl Leavitt, 1894- (Box 2)
    - Huber, Gotthelf Carl, 1865-1934. (Box 2)
    - Hudson, Richard, 1845-1915. (Box 2)
    - Humphreys, Wilber Ray. (Box 2)
    - Hunt, Maurice Patterson. (Box 2)
    - Hunt, Walter Fred, b. 1882. (Box 2)
    - Hussey, William Joseph, 1862-1926. (Box 2)
    - Hutchins, Harry Burns, 1847-1930. (Box 2)
    - Huxford, Walter Scott, 1892-1958. (Box 2)
    - Irving, Pierre Leslie. (Box 2)
    - Isaacs, Raphael, 1891- (Box 2)
  - Jackson-Myers
    - Jackson, George Leroy, 1876-1954. (Box 2)
    - James, Laylin K. (Box 2)
    - James, Preston Everett, 1899- (Box 2)
    - Jamison, Charles Laselle, b. 1885. (Box 2)
    - Jennings, Herbert Spencer, 1868-1947. (Box 2)
    - Jensen, Gordon L. (Box 2)
    - Jobin, Antoine Joseph, b. 1889. (Box 2)
    - Johnson, Elias Finley, 1861-1933. (Box 2)
    - Johnson, Oakley Calvin. (Box 2)
    - Johnson, Otis Coe, 1839-1912. (Box 2)
    - Johnston, Clarence Thomas, 1872-1970. (Box 2)
    - Joiner, Charles Wycliffe, 1916- (Box 2)
    - Jolly [janitor] (Box 2)
    - Jones, Charles Nelson. (Box 2)
    - Jones, Edward David, 1870-1944. (Box 2)
    - Jones, Elisha, 1832-1888. (Box 2)
    - Jones, Howard Mumford, 1892- (Box 2)
    - Jones, Samuel Arthur, 1834-1912. (Box 2)
    - Jordan, Frederick Parker, 1857-1946. (Box 2)
    - Jotter, Ernst Victor, b. 1879. (Box 2)
    - Kahn, Edgar A. (Box 2)
    - Karpinski, Louis Charles, 1878-1956. (Box 2)
    - Kauper, Paul G. (Box 2)
    - Keeler, Hugh Edward, 1889-1964. (Box 2)
    - Keeler, Louis W. (Box 2)
    - Kellum, Lewis Burnett, 1897- (Box 2)
    - Kelsey, Francis Willey, 1858-1927. (Box 2)
    - Kent, Charles Artemas, 1835-1917. (Box 2)
    - Kenyon, Herbert Alden. (Box 2)
    - Kingery, Richard H. (Box 2)
    - Kingsley, Homer Hitchcock. (Box 2)
    - Kinyon, Claudius Bligh, 1851-1924. (Box 2)
    - Kirchner, Otto, 1846-1920. (Box 2)
    - Knowlton, Jerome Cyril, 1850-1916. (Box 3)
    - Knudson, Charles A. (Box 3)
    - Koch, Harlan C. (Box 3)
    - Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941. (Box 3)
    - Koëlla, Charles E. (Box 3)
    - Kraus, Edward Henry, 1875- (Box 3)
    - Kynoch, William. (Box 3)
    - Kyte, George C. (Box 3)
    - Lane, Victor Hugo, 1852-1930. (Box 3)
    - Langley, John Williams, 1841-1918. (Box 3)
    - LaRue, Carl Downey, b. 1888. (Box 3)
    - LaRue, George Roger, 1882-1967. (Box 3)
    - Lawton, Charles DeWitt, 1835-1909. (Box 3)
    - Lee, Alfred Oughton, 1873-1938. (Box 3)
    - Leidy, Paul Allen, b. 1888. (Box 3)
    - Leverett, Frank, 1859-1943. (Box 3)
    - Levi, Moritz. (Box 3)
    - Lewitt, William. (Box 3)
    - Lichty, David Martin, 1862-1942. (Box 3)
    - Liddicoat, Richard Thomas, b. 1891. (Box 3)
    - Lindsay, George Allan, b. 1879. (Box 3)
    - Little, Clarence Cook, 1888-1971. (Box 3)
    - Littlefield, Laura C. (Box 3)
    - Litzenberg, Karl, 1905- (Box 3)
    - Lloyd, Alfred Henry, 1864-1927. (Box 3)
    - Lloyd, Alice Crocker, 1893-1950. (Box 3)
    - Lloyd, Harold Rhys. (Box 3)
    - Lockwood, Albert Lewis, 1871-1933. (Box 3)
    - Lockwood, Samuel P. (Box 3)
    - Loeffler, Egbert Theodore. (Box 3)
    - Loehr, Max Johannes Joseph, 1903-1988. (Box 3)
    - Long, Dwight Clark, 1894- (Box 3)
    - Lord, Robert Howard, 1885-1954. (Box 3)
    - Love, Clyde E. (Clyde Elton), b. 1882. (Box 3)
    - Lovell, Alfred Henry. (Box 3)
    - Lynds, James Gifford. (Box 3)
    - Lyons, Chalmers John, 1874-1935. (Box 3)
    - Lyster, Henry Francis, 1837-1894. (Box 3)
    - McAlpine, Roy K. (Roy Kenneth), b. 1884. (Box 3)
    - McAlvay, Aaron Vance, 1847-1915. (Box 3)
    - McArdle, Richard Edwin, 1899- (Box 3)
    - McCabe, Warren L. (Box 3)
    - McClusky, Howard Y. (Howard Yale), 1900-1982. (Box 3)
    - McConkey, George McDonald. (Box 3)
    - McCotter, Rollo Eugene. (Box 3)
    - McDowell, Robert H. (Box 3)
    - Mack, Charles Samuel, b. 1856. (Box 3)
    - MacKenzie, Roderick Duncan, 1885-1940. (Box 3)
    - MacLachlan, Daniel A. (Box 3)
    - McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947. (Box 3)
    - McLaughlin, Dean B. (Dean Benjamin), 1901-1965. (Box 3)
    - McLaughlin, Lois T. (Lois Thompson) (Box 3)
    - McLaughlin, William Aloysius, b. 1880. (Box 3)
    - MacLean, Donald, 1839-1903. (Box 3)
    - McMurrich, J. Playfair (James Playfair), 1859-1939. (Box 3)
    - McMurry, Kenneth Charles. (Box 3)
    - Maddy, Joseph, 1891-1966. (Box 3)
    - Manace, Bernard A. (Box 3)
    - Manace, Gordon. (Box 3)
    - Manyon, Leonard. (Box 3)
    - Mapel, John Jamison. (Box 3)
    - Marin, Axel. (Box 3)
    - Markley, Joseph Lybrand, 1859-1930. (Box 3)
    - Marshall, Mark. (Box 3)
    - Marshall, Walter V. (Box 3)
    - Marshall, William. (Box 3)
    - Martin, James Nelson, d. 1913. (Box 3)
    - Mattern, David Earl, 1890-1959. (Box 3)
    - Matthews, Donald M. (Box 3)
    - Maxwell, Allen Douglas. (Box 3)
    - Maxwell, James H. (Box 3)
    - May, George Augustus, 1872-1948. (Box 3)
    - Meader, Clarence Linton, 1868-1967. (Box 3)
    - Mechem, Floyd R. (Floyd Russell), 1858-1928. (Box 3)
    - Meinicke, Bruno, b. 1888. (Box 3)
    - Menefee, F. N. (Ferdinand Northrup), 1886-1973. (Box 3)
    - Menge, Walter O. (Box 3)
    - Mensel, Ernst Heinrich, b. 1865. (Box 3)
    - Merlino, Camillo Pascal, 1900- (Box 3)
    - Merrick, Howard B. (Box 3)
    - Merriman, George Benjamin. (Box 3)
    - Merritt, Benjamin D. (Box 3)
    - Meyer, Frances. (Box 3)
    - Michaels, Anne C. (Box 3)
    - Michaels, Joseph J. (Box 3)
    - Mickle, Frank Alexander. (Box 3)
    - Miggett, William Lincoln. (Box 3)
    - Miller, Norman F. (Box 3)
    - Milliman, George E. (Box 3)
    - Minifie, Fred. (Box 3)
    - Mitchell, Elmer Dayton, 1889- (Box 3)
    - Mitchell, Thomas Joseph. (Box 3)
    - Mooney, Edward L. (Box 3)
    - Moore, Allan Nelson. (Box 3)
    - Moore, Arthur Dearth, 1895- (Box 3)
    - Moore, Samuel. (Box 3)
    - Morgan, John Coleman. (Box 3)
    - Morris, George Sylvester, 1840-1889. (Box 3)
    - Morris, Victoria. (Box 3)
    - Morrison, Roger Leroy, 1883- (Box 3)
    - Mosher, Eliza, 1846-1928. (Box 3)
    - Mueschke, Paul. (Box 3)
    - Mulford, Walter. (Box 3)
    - Munster, Norman L. (Box 3)
    - Murtland, Cleo, 1873-1965. (Box 3)
    - Muyskens, John Henry. (Box 3)
    - Myers, George Edmund, b. 1871. (Box 3)
  - Nagele-Swinton
    - Nagele, Gregor, d. 1900. [janitor] (Box 3)
    - Nancrede, Charles Beylard Guerard de, 1847-1921. (Box 3)
    - Nelson, Erwin Ellis, b. 1881. (Box 3)
    - Nelson, Joseph Raleigh, 1873-1961. (Box 3)
    - Nelson, Lyle Morgan, 1918- (Box 3)
    - Nelson, Norman E. (Box 3)
    - Newburgh, Louis Harry. (Box 3)
    - Newcomb, William Wilmot. (Box 3)
    - Newcombe, Frederick Charles, 1858-1927. (Box 3)
    - Niehuss, Marvin Lemmon, 1903- (Box 3)
    - Nordmeyer, Henry W. (Henry Waldemar), 1891-1980. (Box 3)
    - Northrop, Phillip M. (Box 3)
    - Norton, Newell A. (Box 3)
    - Novy, Frederick George, 1864-1957. (Box 3)
    - Obetz, Henry Lorenz, d. 1913. (Box 3)
    - O'Dell, Frederick Charles. (Box 3)
    - Okkelberg, Peter Olaus, 1880- (Box 3)
    - Olmsted, Charles Thomas. (Box 3)
    - Olney, Edward, 1827-1887. (Box 3)